♪ Men... ♪
I can't believe you've managed
to stay in this house.
You're like
a human barnacle.
Thanks, Mom.
Oh, I wasn't putting
you down, sweetheart.
It's good that you have a skill.
Did you come over for a reason,
or just to insult me?
The two aren't
mutually exclusive.
Mom.
Charlie's bank
contacted me.
Seems he had a secret
safe deposit box.
I knew it! I knew he had to
have something squirreled away.
Naturally, I went right
down there to check it out.
So what was in it? Cash?
Diamonds? Krugerrands?
Want to wipe your mouth?
You're drooling a little.
Sorry.
Actually, I was quite surprised
about what was in there.
- Oh, tell me, tell me!
- I'll do better than that.
Here.
I'm pretty sure he
wanted you to have this.
Oh boy, oh boy, oh boy...
I knew you'd look out
for me, big bro.
What the hell is this?
Charlie's journal.
Charlie kept a journal?
Your brother was
a very complex man.
Perhaps he needed a safe place
to express his deepest emotions
and innermost thoughts,
or some such nonsense.
No. No cash, dear.
Already checked.
Of course not.
Why leave cash to your
impoverished brother
when you can leave your
alcohol-muddled thoughts?
Yay.
"To whom it may concern,
"if you are reading this it
means either my heart or lungs
"finally gave out.
"Or I rejected my new liver.
"Or my brother wouldn't
give me a piece of his.
"Or I choked on my own vomit,
"or somebody else's.
Or some crazy chick
pushed me in front of a bus..."
Ooh, so close.
Well, I hope reading it brings
you some comfort and closure.
Are you sure that's all that
was in the safe deposit box?
Yes.
So my brother went
out to the bank
and rented a safe deposit box
just for this journal?
It would appear so.
That makes no sense.
He intimated on many occasions
that he had some cash
stashed away for emergencies...
you know, like getting
a hooker after an earthquake.
Sweetheart, you have to
stop living in the past.
What's done is done.
Start looking forward.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Is that a new watch?
No.
You have your whole
life ahead of you,
and the fact is, you and I are
all that's left of this family.
Well...
you, me and Jake.
Hey, Grandma.
Whoa. Thought that was
coming out the other end.
You're right.
It's just you and me.
That looks like a man's Cartier.
It's a knock-off.
My point is,
with Charlie gone,
you and I have to learn
how to help and support
one another no matter what.
Gee, that would be great.
You were always
the good son.
Now you're my only son.
Oh, Mommy.
Oh, Walden!
How nice to see you!
It's a miracle
I'm not a transsexual
on Dancing With the Stars.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, men, manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ohh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Men, men, men,  manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ah. ♪
♪ Men. ♪
♪ Two and a Half Men 9x07 ♪
Those Fancy Japanese Toilets
Original Air Date on October 31, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
I must tell you, Walden,
it's so nice to finally
see someone in this house
who surfs for something
other than porn.
Yeah, I love the ocean.
Just you alone with
your thoughts.
Time standing still, at peace
with the entire universe.
Plus, you can pee in it
and nobody knows.
Charming.
Actually, I'm glad
you stopped by.
Um... Do you know a good
interior designer?
As a matter of fact,
I know a great one.
Evelyn Harper Interior Design.
I thought you were
a real estate agent.
I am. I'm also
a building inspector,
mortgage broker, notary
public and a bail bondsman.
A bail bondsman?
Admittedly, that business has
slowed down since my son died.
But getting back to your needs,
what did you have in mind
in terms of redecorating?
I don't know.
I just, I just want my home
to reflect who I am.
And who are you?
I've got a buttload of money,
but I'm a pretty simple guy.
I... like people, but
I don't entertain a lot.
Oh, I'm not a neat freak,
but I don't like clutter.
Oh, you know, and the most
important thing is,
I want the house to use
green renewable energy,
you know, like solar
power and wind power...
Unless Brookstone or
somebody comes out with
a home nuclear reactor,
because, I mean, come on,
who wouldn't want one of those?
"A buttload of money""
You're in good hands.
This journal is unbelievable.
You aren't thinking of
publishing it, are you?
What? Of course not, why?
Well, I'm shoppin' around
my own Charlie memoir.
It's called Man Whore.
It's catchy.
But there was more to
Charlie than we thought.
I mean, listen to this.
"I just sent a girl home
who told me she loved me
"and I can't even
remember her name.
"What is wrong with me
that I just have
"anonymous drunken encounters
night after night?
"Do I drink to fill
the loneliness,
or to hide from the
horror I've become?"
You know, I feel awful that
I lived with him for so long
and I didn't recognize his pain.
"I remember, her name is Rachel!
"I feel better now.
I'll reward myself with some
cocaine and an Asian hooker."
So remember, the key to
balancing the equation
is to place coefficients
in front of each reactant
and product so that
all the atoms balance.
I bet you shower every day.
Jake, we're supposed
to be studying
for the chemistry mid-term.
I'd rather study our chemistry.
Lame.
Really? I thought it
was a "double intendo."
Hey, guys.
Whatcha studying?
Chemistry.
Cool.
Looks like you two
have a little chemistry.
That's so clever.
I'm Megan.
Oh, hi, Megan. It's nice
to meet you. I'm Walden.
Oh, are you the Walden
that bought the house?
Yeah, how many Waldens
have you met lately?
That's... that's so funny.
And I'm lame.
Well, it was nice to meet you.
I'll let you guys get
back to your "chemistry."
Bye, Walden!
It was nice meeting you too.
You know, if he hooks up
with you, he goes to jail.
I'd wait for him.
"Peed blood again this morning.
Should I be worried?"
As it turns out, no.
We have to get
rid of Walden.
- We do?
- Oh yeah, he's gotta go.
Does it occur to you
that this is his house
and if anybody goes,
it's gonna be us?
Actually, no.
What's the problem?
He's stealing my girlfriend.
Wait, I thought
she was your tutor.
Think about it, Dad.
Would I have asked for a tutor
if I didn't have a... what do
you call it, interior motive?
Go on.
She's only interested in
glomming onto Walden.
Well, if it makes
you feel any better,
I think my own mother likes
him more than she likes me.
Why would that
make me feel better?
I honestly don't know.
Is this what I have to
look forward to in life?
Always losing girls to
smarter, better-looking men?
Well, think of it this way:
you're carrying on a
proud family tradition.
Hello, dear.
What's all this?
Oh, didn't you know?
I'm helping young
Thor redecorate.
I hope that's
all you're doing.
Whatever do you mean?
He's tall, he's handsome,
he's vulnerable,
and you're old enough
to be his ancestor.
Relax, Alan.
The only thing I want
to pull out of that boy's
pants is his wallet.
You sure?
Believe me, I have
no ulterior motive.
I believe that's
"interior," Grandma.
You really should get that boy a
unicycle and some juggling pins.
Evelyn, cool, you're here.
Uh, could you come on up?
There's some things I want
you to do in my bedroom.
Give the customer
what he wants.
Okay, to start with,
I want grey Carrara
marble counters,
a steam shower...
oh, and can we get one of
those fancy Japanese toilets
that sprays water and
cleans your tushie?
With your money you could afford
an actual Japanese
person to do it.
See what you can find.
Okay, in here, I would like
to replace the bed frame,
the curtains, the dresser,
the end tables and the lamps.
All right.
What would you like
to replace them with?
Um...
A cooler bed frame,
cooler curtains, cooler dresser,
cooler end tables
and cooler lamps.
"Cooler." I'm on it.
Uh, now, would you
like to repaint?
Hey, can I have walls
that change color
depending on my mood?
No.
But we could paint them white
and get you an industrial
strength antidepressant.
That will work too.
Would you like to
keep the camera?
What camera?
Aw...
Awesome!
I'm on TV.
Hello!
I am so keeping that.
All right. Anything else?
Can I have a Jacuzzi
on the balcony?
'Cause I'm single now,
so I'm going to be
having sex with a lot of
women I haven't met yet.
Oh... I just got an idea!
Just out of curiosity, what kind
of woman are you attracted to?
There's my wife.
Oh, and there's women
who look like my wife.
That's very romantic.
Oh, and Ellen DeGeneres.
I don't know
what it is.
Whether it's the slacks
or the way she dances--
it's hot.
♪ Men. ♪
You're up early.
Charlie's journal-- I
can't stop reading it.
Listen to this.
"My brother's kid
showed up today.
"He's kind of cute.
"No way he's really Alan's kid.
"And best of all,
he's smart as a whip.
I think he's got
a very bright future."
Oh, that just
breaks my heart.
Yeah.
We were all so young
and naive then.
Hey.
What? I took a huge dump.
No way he's really my kid.
You look very pretty today.
Jake, I'm here
to study.
The test was yesterday.
I already failed.
Hey, guys.
Hey, Walden.
Here we go.
Whoa, Megan,
you look very pretty today.
Thanks.
You look pretty, too.
Thank you.
Where are you going?
Oh, I am going furniture
shopping with Jake's grandma.
Oh, I love furniture.
And grandmas.
Cool.
See ya.
Okay, Megan,
I know what's going on here
and I really don't appreciate...
What's that about?
I don't know. I'm
just in the mood.
Okay.
Come on.
Where are we going?
To your room.
Okay.
Hello, gorgeous.
Did you miss me?
'Cause I sure missed you.
Let me pull this thing
out of you.
Are you gonna turn your car off?
I did.
Might need service.
Sadly, that's where
I just came from.
You know what's great
about my electric car?
What?
I just turned it on.
Sweet.
So where you headed?
Um, I'm going
to pick up your mom.
We're going furniture shopping.
Okay, well, just
a little heads up
before you journey to
the caves of Mordor.
My mother has what
you might call
a, uh, proclivity
for younger men.
You mean she's like a cougar?
No, she's not
"like a cougar""
she's the mother
of all cougars.
So kind of an uber-cougar?
A super duper
uber-cougar.
You think a bit of better butter
would make
her bitter batter better?
What?
I just like saying that.
Walden, I'm
serious here.
Don't worry.
I'm not going to hook up
with your mom.
Yeah, if I had a dime for
every time I heard that,
I'd have $3.60.
And I know that doesn't
sound like a lot,
but it is 36 times.
That's a very weird thing
to keep track of.
I got a lot
of free time.
Trust me,
nothing's going to happen.
Okay. But try not to
hurt her feelings.
I mean, she may be a rapacious
sexual predator,
but she breaks
just like a little girl.
Understood.
Oh, hey, check it out.
I got voice control.
Lights on.
Radio on.
Back up.
Bye!
Well, you may not be
pretty or expensive,
but you get me
where I want to go.
Thank you for walking
me to my door.
You don't meet many
gentlemen nowadays.
You're welcome.
Is that a camera?
Hello!
Would you like to come in
for a drink before you go?
I don't know,
I should probably get going.
What's your hurry?
I just think that
we should keep
our relationship business
and not "biznass."
Oh, my goodness,
do you think I'm hitting on you?
W-Well, Alan did say
that you're an uber-cougar.
An uber-cougar?
A super duper uber-cougar.
Oh, my Lord.
Now, you listen to me,
young man.
My son has some serious issues.
And he tends to imagine things.
Believe me, I have no carnal
designs on you whatsoever.
Really?
For God's sake, Walden, I'm old
enough to be your mother.
Assuming a teenage pregnancy
of course.
Okay, sure.
I'll have a drink.
Are you going to tell Alan?
I'm going to tell everyone.
♪ Men. ♪
"Alan moved in with
his girlfriend yesterday.
"How stupid is she?
"Oh, well, doesn't matter.
"Like a nonspecific
urinary infection,
"I'm sure he'll be back
before long.
"Truth be told,
I actually kind of miss
"the jug-eared freeloader.
How stupid am I?"
I don't believe it.
He loved me.
My brother loved me.
"Speaking of stupid,
"today I bought
a $100,000 Cartier watch.
"But I'm afraid to wear it,
so I'm gonna keep it
in my safe deposit box."
Son of a bitch!
That was, that was great.
Just-Just great.
Thank you so much.
Hey.
Hey. How'd it go
with my mom?
Fine, fine.
Just shopped for furniture.
Rugs, chairs and tables.
Nice.
Armoires, ottomans,
curtains, recliners,
love seats, throw pillows.
Okay, good night.
Oh, yeah, she did him.
Bye. Thanks again!
Hey, dude, how you doing?
Fantastic.
I love you, man.
Thanks.
What an affectionate family.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==